<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<BlogPosts>
	<BlogPost>
		<Id>0</Id>
		<Category>HTML5</Category>
		<Subject>CryptoHansClub : May 01, 2022 – May 08, 2022</Subject>
		<DateString>2022-01-26 12:00:00</DateString>
		<ImageUrl>https://nftcalendar.io/storage/uploads/events/2022/4/CYtHwL3Alhp7sVQ1V7Jotb1kvJ5Oj0btdNXurvqy.webp</ImageUrl>
		<Body>
			The Crypto Hans Club is a private collection of 7.777 unique hand-drawn Funny Horses NFTs pieces collected on the Ethereum Blockchain. Artist Maya Delia. The collection is updated every week and the price increases every time! All NFTs are created only by hand without automatic generation. Get paid every month just for owning Hans NFT! More information in our Discord section payments.
		</Body>
	</BlogPost>
	<BlogPost>
		<Id>1</Id>
		<Category>HTML5</Category>
		<Subject>Business Bears Club : May 01, 2022 – May 08, 2022</Subject>
		<DateString>2022-02-17 12:00:00</DateString>
		<ImageUrl>https://nftcalendar.io/storage/uploads/2022/04/25/bbc_gif_042520221716386266d776273e9.gif</ImageUrl>
		<Body>
			It is the mission of the Business Bears club to create an exclusive place where future business models, important decisions, and partnerships will be defined. It will be a place where investors and startups can meet, where holders will get 20% of sales to build their own business, and it will be a club that helps bears and forest in critical regions around the world. Four months were spent working round the clock on the Business Bears club's design by 10 different designers until now. With our project, we want to redefine a bench market in terms of design for NFTs. We carefully reviewed and considered every detail of our 10’000 NFTs collection. Each bear was created in 4k resolution and the entire collection has over 500 high-quality traits. Besides the design, our 2 animators worked for 3 weeks on the teaser video. The video shows our bear at one of our planned utilities. The collection represents the Business Bears club and only those who own one of the 10'000 bears will have access to the club and utilites. Our international team includes a very young and talented team as well as three experienced older designers. It's a great mix of skills and experience. We focused on every detail from sculpting to topology, rigging, grooming, texturing and finishing. It is very important to us that our community receives a well-thought-out work of art!
		</Body>
	</BlogPost>
	<BlogPost>
		<Id>2</Id>
		<Category>HTML5</Category>
		<Subject>Cybee DAO NFT with Passive Income : May 01, 2022 – May 08, 2022</Subject>
		<DateString>2022-01-21 12:00:00</DateString>
		<ImageUrl>https://nftcalendar.io/storage/uploads/events/2022/4/iaJrgch3QEDEP0Dr6mQiuuZTkFPZc3CJw0fVCzFi.webp</ImageUrl>
		<Body>
			Cybee DAO aims to establish the biggest NFT community and a huge Dapp and GameFi ecosystem that provides passive income and benefits for all holders. Once you mint a Cybee, you will get the Cybee DAO membership and $CBD token rewards. Meanwhile, you can get the ticket to Invite to Earn and earn ETH rewards, receive 3D Cybee and NFT Derivatives airdrop and play to earn $CBD in Cybee Ecosystem.	In addition to the appreciation of NFT, Cybee DAO will distribute a portion of the net revenue to all holders at a fixed time, such as quarterly or annually. The amount will be calculated based on the proportion to their holdings.
		</Body>
	</BlogPost>
	<BlogPost>
		<Id>3</Id>
		<Category>HTML5</Category>
		<Subject>Rebirth Of Surrealism : May 01, 2022 – May 07, 2022</Subject>
		<DateString>2021-12-28 12:00:00</DateString>
		<ImageUrl>https://nftcalendar.io/storage/uploads/2022/04/28/9dkap8hmyz61iixyvedl_042820220035206269e148edb03.jpg</ImageUrl>
		<Body>
			"Rebirth Of Surrealism" is a collection of uniquely created, Surreal, 8K-3D images and MP4 videos. Each creation is an intricate work of art -that can never be duplicated. We love our NFT community! Stay trippy friends and please enjoy our "Rebirth" collection
		</Body>
	</BlogPost>
</BlogPosts>